Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Production, Art and Design, Photographs and Negatives, Office Files of Laura Walworth and Dayna Bealy FA1819
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office Files of Dayna Bealy, 1997-2000; 2; 9.4 Cubic Feet 22 containers
  - 1136 - UCLA Inroads/Asia Conference, RGA 965-1380, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), 1997 August (Box 11, Folder 116)
    8 4x6 prints
  - 1137 - Mozambique/CAMPFIRE, Communal Wildlife Management, ABCD/PSJ/Environmental Development, Henner Frankenfeld, photographer, 1997 October 22 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    22 black and white contact sheets, 21 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1138 - Kibera Community Self Help Program, Nairobi, Kenya, Wendy Stone, photographer, 1997 November (Box 11, Folder 118)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 7 4x6 prints,
  - 1138A - Kibera Healthcare Trust Nairobi, Kenya, Wendy Stone, photographer, 1997 November (Box 11, Folder 119)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1138B - SIDARC (Slums Information Development and Resource Centre), Nairobi, Wendy Stone, photographer, 1997 November (Box 11, Folder 120)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 1 4x6 photo
  - 1138C - Kenya Association of Professional Counsellors (KAPC), Wendy Stone, photographer, 1997 November (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - 1139 - Annual Report 1997, Small Enterprise Development Agency (Assets-Economic Development), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 11, Folder 122)
    7 black and white contact sheets, 11 8x10 prints, 7 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1140 - Annual Report 1997, African Wildlife Foundation, Assets-Community and Resource Development, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 11, Folder 123)
    Grant 965-0834
    1 contact sheet, 2 8x10 prints, 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1141 - Annual Report 1997, National Museum of Kenya (Kuona Trust), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Wendy Stone, photographer, 1997 November (Box 11, Folder 124)
    2 contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints, 2 4x6 prints
  - Annual Report 1997, Photos Correspondence, Nigeria (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - 1142 - 1997 Annual Report, Community Life Project (CLP), Vulcanizers Cooperative Association, Nigeria, 1997 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    3 contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 4 4x6 black and white photos
  - 1143 - Annual Report 1997, Jazz 38 Tree In My Life, Nigeria, 1997 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    1 contact sheet, 3 black and white 4x6 photos
  - 1144 - Annual Report 1997, Farmers Development Unions (FADU), Ibadan, 1997 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    1 contact sheet, 1 black and white 8x10, 3 4x6 black and white photos
  - 1145 - Annual Report 1997, Association for Reproductive and Family Health (ARFH), Ibadan, Nigeria, 1997 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - 1146 - Winter Report 1998, Desire, New Orleans, Louisiana, Tom Roster, photographer, 1997 November (Box 12, Folder 130)
    10 contact sheets, 7 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1147 - Ronald Richardson, W. E. B. Du Bois African American Research Center, Harvard University, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Stella Johnson, photographer, 1997 November (Box 12, Folder 131)
    5 contact sheets, 3 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1148 - Mohammad Yunus, Founder Grameen Bank Speaking at the Ford Foundation, Don Pollard, photographer, 1997 November (Box 12, Folder 132)
    5 contact sheets, 2 8x10 black and white photos
  - 1148 - Mohammad Yunus, Founder, Grameen Bank, Speaking at the Ford Foundation, Don Pollard, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 343)
  - 1149 - Anna Deavere Smith, Coffee Hour Conversations, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Tracy Litt/Impact Visuals, photographer, 1997 February 19 (Box 12, Folder 133)
    4 contact sheets, 12 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1150 - Winter Report 1998, Meet the Composer, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Steve Wewerka, photographer (Box 12, Folder 134)
    4 black and white contact sheets, copies of contact sheets
  - 1150 - Winter Report 1998, Meet the Composer, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Steve Wewerka, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 344)
  - 1151 - Winter Report 1998, Earnest Johnson, Federation of Southern Coop, Tom Roster, photographer, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    6 contact sheets, 4 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1152 - Winter Report 1998, Individual Development Account, Linda Zelinda Davis-Kirk, Paul L. Merideth, photographer, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 136)
    5 contact sheets, 1 8x10 black and white print
  - 1152 - Winter Report 1998, Individual Development Account, Linda Zelinda Davis-Kirk, Paul L. Merideth, photographer - negatives, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 345)
  - 1153 - Winter Report 1998, Walter Robinson, Meet the Composer, John Goodman, photographer (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - 1154 - Winter Report 1998, Michael Sherraden for IDA Story, Photo Credit: Kuhlmann & Associates Photography (Box 12, Folder 138)
    5 contact sheets, 1 5x7 print
  - 1154 - Winter Report 1998, Michael Sherraden for IDA Story, Kuhlmann & Associates Photography - negatives (Box 27, Folder 346)
  - 1156 - Annual Report 1997, Crossing Borders, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Education, Knowledge, and Religion, Philip Greenberg, photographer, 1998 January 23 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    5 contact sheets, 1 5x7 photo
  - 1156 - Annual Report 1997, Crossing Borders, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Education, Knowledge, and Religion, Philip Greenberg, photographer - negatives, 1998 January 23 (Box 27, Folder 347)
    4 sets of negatives
  - 1157 - Annual Report 1997, Blackfeet Development Fund, Assets-Community and Resource Development, Andy Geiger, photographer, 1998 January 23 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    13 contact sheets, 6 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1157 - Annual Report 1997, Blackfeet Development Fund, Assets, Community and Resource Development, Andy Geiger, photographer - negatives, 1998 January 23 (Box 27, Folder 348)
    13 sets of negatives
  - 1158 - Annual Reports 1997 and 1998, Indonesia-Agroforestry, Assets-Community Resource Development, Chris Stowers/Panos, photographer, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 141)
    24 contact sheets, 14 8x10 prints, 36 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1159 - Winter 1998, Philanthropy Conference in London, Mark Hakansson/Panos, photographer, 1997 October 14-16 (Box 13, Folder 142)
    5 contact sheets, 9 8x10 prints, 1 5x7 black and white print
  - 1160 - Annual Report 1997, Gauteng Music Academy, PWV Music Academy, South Africa, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Media, Arts, and Culture, Jodi Bieber/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 13, Folder 143)
    15 black and white 8x10 prints, 1 8x10 black and white transparency, 24 black and white photocopies
  - 1161 - Annual Report 1997, Linda Darling Hammond, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Education, Knowledge, Religion (EKR), Mark Ludak, photographer (Box 13, Folder 144)
    3 contact sheets, 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1161 - Annual Report 1997, Linda Darling Hammond, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Education, Knowledge, Religion (EKR), Mark Ludak, photographer - negatives (Box 27, Folder 349)
  - 1162 - Annual Report 1997, Center for Policy Alternatives, Linda Tarr Whelan, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Philip Greenberg, photographer (Box 13, Folder 145)
    3 contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1162 - Annual Report 1997, Center for Policy Alternatives, Linda Tarr Whelan, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Philip Greenberg, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 350)
  - 1163A - Annual Report 1997, Radio Geronimo (FAP) (979-0006), Indonesia, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Mr. Tatan Sjuflana, photographer (Box 13, Folder 146)
    8 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1163B - Annual Report 1997, Institute of Research, Education, and Publications (950-0529-1), Indonesia, Assets-Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH) (Box 13, Folder 147)
    4 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1163C - Annual Report 1997, Government of Republic of Indonesia, Ministry of Health (940-0735-2), Assets-Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH) (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - 1164 - Annual Report 1997, BEES Trust, South Africa, Assets: Economic Development, 960-1060, Jodi Bieber, photographer (Box 13, Folder 149)
    6 contact sheets, 6 8x10 and 7 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1165 - Annual Report 1997, Aalochana Centre for Documentation and Research on Women, (960-0918), Piers Benatar/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 14, Folder 150)
    9 contact sheets, 6 8x10 and 21 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1166 - Annual Report 1997, Center for Communications and Cultural Action, India, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Piers Benatar/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 14, Folder 151)
    14 contact sheets, 5 8x10 and 33 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1167 - Annual Report 1997, Indian Grameen Services, India, Assets, Piers Benatar/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 14, Folder 152)
    13 contact sheets, 2 8x10 and 18 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1168 - Annual Report 1997, YR Gaitonde Medical, Educational, and Research Foundation, Assets, 960-0518, Piers Benatar/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 14, Folder 153)
    4 contact sheets, 6 8x10 and 7 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1169 - Annual Report 1997, Campus Diversity, India, #44F Farook and D.H.V. College (Box 14, Folder 154)
    2 contact sheets, 17 8x10 and 8 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1169 - Annual Report 1997, Campus Diversity, India, #44F Farook and D.H.V. College - negatives (Box 28, Folder 351)
  - 1170 - Annual Report 1997, University of Natal-South Africa, 960-1041, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Education, Knowledge, Religion (EKR) Paul Weinberg/Panos (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - 1171A - Annual Report 1998, Amazonia/Desenvolvimento Sustentavol, Brazil, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer (Box 14, Folder 156)
    9 contact sheets, 9 8x10 and 13 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1171B - Annual Report 1997, Brazil, Afro-Reggae Group, Brazil, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer (Box 15, Folder 157)
    5 contact sheets, 3 8x10 and 5 4x6 prints
  - 1171C - Annual Report 1997, ABIA/VERJ, Brazil, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer (Box 15, Folder 158)
    3 contact sheets, 5 8x10 and 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1171D - Annual Report 1997, Niteroi/Family Doctor Program, Brazil, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer (Box 15, Folder 159)
    5 contact sheets, 2 8x10 and 1 4x6 black and prints
  - Annual Report 1997 Correspondence - Brazil (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - 1172A - Annual Report 1997, Women's Study Group, "Rosario Castellanos," Assets, Reproductive Health and Population, Mexico, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 15, Folder 161)
    4 contact sheets, 4 8x10 and 2 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1172B - Annual Report 1997, Mexico, CIESAS Photography Project, San Cristobal, Chiapas, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 15, Folder 162)
    4 contact sheets, 1 8x10 and 2 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1172C - Annual Report 1997, Heriberto Jara Center, Mexico, Peace and Social Justice, Governance and Civil Society, Jeremy Horner/Panos, photographer, 1998 January (Box 15, Folder 163)
    3 contact sheets, 2 8x10 and 3 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1172D - Annual Report 1997, Cooperative Housing Foundation, Assets, Mexico, Jeremy Horner/Panos, 1998 January (Box 15, Folder 164)
    5 contact sheets, 4 8x10 and 1 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1172E - Annual Report 1997, Assets, Environmental Defense Fund, Mexico, Jeremy Horner/Panos, 1998 January (Box 15, Folder 165)
    4 contact sheets, 2 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1172F - Annual Report 1997, OPCION, EMAC, Jeremy Horner/Panos, 1998 January (Box 15, Folder 166)
    1 contact sheets, 2 8x10 and 2 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1173 - Annual Report 1997, Assets, Mar Vista Family Center, Assets Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Jeff Jacobson (Box 15, Folder 167)
    14 contact sheets, 8 8x10 and 18 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1173 - Annual Report 1997, Assets, Mar Vista Family Center, Assets Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Jeff Jacobson - negatives (Box 28, Folder 352)
    14 sets of negatives
  - 1174 - Annual Report 1997, EMAC, Judy Mitoma, Jeff Jacobson, photographer (Box 15, Folder 168)
    7 contact sheets, 3 8x10 and 8 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1174 - Annual Report 1997, EMAC, Judy Mitoma, Jeff Jacobson, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 353)
  - 1175 - Annual Report 1997, Assets, Economic Development, Coastal Enterprises, Stella Johnson, photographer (Box 15, Folder 169)
    9 contact sheets, 3 8x10 and 9 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1176 - Annual Report 1997, Assets Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Union of Palestinian Medical Relief Committees, Jerusalem, West Bank, Rula Halawana, photographer (Box 15, Folder 170)
    8 8x10 and 10 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1177 - Annual Report 1997, Assets PRI, Rural Enterprise/Rose Jasperson, Norman Mauskopf/Matrix, photographers (Box 16, Folder 171)
    17 contact sheets, 9 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1177 - Annual Report 1997, Assets PRI, Rural Enterprise/Rose Jasperson, Norman Mauskopf/Matrix, photographers - negatives (Box 28, Folder 354)
  - 1178 - Annual Report 1997, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture, Education, Knowledge, Religion, Crossing Borders, Jeffry Scott, photographers (Box 16, Folder 172)
    11 contact sheets, 16 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1179 - Annual Report 1997, Peace and Social Justice, Governance and Civil Society, Public/Private Ventures, Jennifer Warburg, photographer (Box 16, Folder 173)
    9 contacts
  - 1180 - Annual Report 1997, Assets Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Wellesley College, Stella Johnson, photographer (Box 16, Folder 174)
    8 contact sheets, 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1181 - Annual Report 1997 - Assets: Economic Development, CARESBAC, Poland, Stuart Franklin/Magnum Photos, photographer (Box 16, Folder 175)
    8 contact sheets, 5 8x10 and 10 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1182 - Annual Report 1997 - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Michael Kraus Lecture, Middlebury College, A.J. Wolfe/Impact Visuals, photographer (Box 16, Folder 176)
    7 contact sheets, 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1182 - Annual Report 1997 - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Michael Kraus Lecture, Middlebury College, A.J. Wolfe/Impact Visuals, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 355)
  - 1183 - Annual Report 1997, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, Ohio, Nicole Bengiveno/Matrix, photographer, 1998 February (Box 16, Folder 177)
    13 contact sheets, 8 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1183 - Annual Report 1997, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, Ohio, Nicole Bengiveno/Matrix, photographer - negatives, 1998 February (Box 28, Folder 356)
  - 1184 - Annual Report 1997 - Good Neighbor Grants, Philip Greenberg, photographer (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - 1184 - Annual Report 1997 - Good Neighbor Grants, Philip Greenberg, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 357)
  - 1185 - Annual Report 1997 - Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Governance and Civil Society (GCS), The Foundation Center, Philip Greenberg (Box 16, Folder 179)
  - 1185 - Annual Report 1997 - Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Governance and Civil Society (GCS), The Foundation Center, Philip Greenberg - negatives (Box 28, Folder 358)
  - 1186 - Partners for Fragile Family's Demonstration Project, Assets, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Planning Grant Announcement and Technical Assistance Meeting Agenda, 1998 February 19 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - 1186 - Partners for Fragile Family's Demonstration Project, Assets, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Don Pollard, photographer - negatives, 1998 February (Box 28, Folder 359)
  - Annual Report 1997, Photos Correspondence - Vietnam (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - 1187A - Annual Report 1997, Vietnam, Hanoi Office, CRES - Vietnam National University (Box 16, Folder 182)
    2 8x10 and 3 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1187B - Annual Report 1997 - Vietnam, Hanoi Office, Institute of Ethnology, Assets, (National Center for Social Sciences and Humanities) (Box 16, Folder 183)
    6 contact sheets, 11 8x10 prints
  - 1187C - Annual Report 1997, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Vietnam, Hanoi Office, National Economics University (NEU) and Street Scenes, Nguyen Hong Sam, photographer, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 184)
    6 contact sheets, 10 8x10 and 16 4x6 prints
  - 1187D - Vietnam, Hanoi Office, Museum of Ethnology, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), National Center for Social Sciences and Humanities, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 185)
    1 contact sheet, 6 8x10 and 4 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1189 - Spring Report 1998, Project GRAD, Jefferson Davis High School, Houston, Texas, Stephen Shames/Matrix, photographer (Box 17, Folder 186)
    4 color and 12 black and white contact sheets, 7 8x10 black and white prints, 2 5x7 color prints
  - 1190 - Spring 1998, Project GRAD, Principal Cole and Tenneco CEO James Ketelson, Houston, Texas, Janice Rubin, photographer, 1998 April (Box 17, Folder 187)
    39 slides
  - 1191 - Spring 1998, Tomas Rivera Policy Institute, for Briefly Noted, Kristen Artz, photographer (Box 17, Folder 188)
    4 contact sheets, 7 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1192 - Spring 1998, Coastal Enterprises, Inc., Assets/Economic Development, A.J. Wolfe/Impact Visuals, photographer, 1998 April 30 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    19 contact sheets, 13 8x10 and 29 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1193 - Annual Report 1997, Chinatown, Philip Greenberg, photographer, 1998 February 11 (Box 17, Folder 190)
    5 contact sheets, 3 8x10 and 7 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1193 - Annual Report 1997, Chinatown, Philip Greenberg, photographer - negatives, 1998 February 11 (Box 28, Folder 360)
  - 1194 - Spring Report 1998, ACCION International, Story, J and L Statuary, Brooklyn, Mark Peterson/SABA, photographer (Box 17, Folder 191)
    10 contact sheets, 3 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1194 - Spring Report 1998, ACCION International, Story, J and L Statuary, Brooklyn, Mark Peterson/SABA, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 361)
    10 sets of negatives
  - 1195 - Spring Report 1998, ACCION International, Michael Chu, Kelly Campbell, photographer (Box 17, Folder 192)
    12 contact sheets, 3 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1196 - Press Conference at Ford Foundation with Fannie Mae and Self-Help, Don Pollard, photographer, 1998 July 23 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    6 contact sheets, 4 4x6, 10 5x7 prints
  - 1196 - Press Conference at Ford Foundation with Fannie Mae and Self-Help, Don Pollard, photographer - negatives, 1998 July 23 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    2 4x5 and 7 8x10 copy negatives, 6 sets of negatives
  - 1197 - Fall Report 1998, Human Rights USA, Atlanta, Georgia, Rob Amberg, photographers, 1998 August 31 (Box 18, Folder 194)
    4 contact sheets, 4 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1198 - Fall Report 1998, Human Rights Special/CELS, Buenos Aires, Argentina, Horacio Poane, photographer (Box 18, Folder 195)
    4 contact sheets, 8 8x10 black and white prints, 3 6x9 color prints
  - 1198 - Fall Report 1998, Human Rights Special/CELS, Buenos Aires, Argentina, Horacio Poane, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 363)
  - 1199 - Fall Report 1998, South Africa/Black Sash, Human Rights Special, Louise Gubb, photographer (Box 18, Folder 196)
    2 contact sheets, 3 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1199 - Fall Report 1998, South Africa/Black Sash, Human Rights Special, Louise Gubb, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 364)
  - 1200 - Fall Report 1998, Human Rights/Indonesia/APIK, Chris Stowers/Panos, photographer (Box 18, Folder 197)
    7 contact sheets, 8 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1201 - Encuentro Feminista Conference, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), SUNY Albany, San Juan, Puerto Rico, Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1998 April 22-24 (Box 18, Folder 198)
    9 contact sheets, 17 black and white prints
  - 1202 - Partnership for National Service and the San Francisco Urban Americorps Collective, Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1998 May 18-20 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    11 contact sheets, 19 8x10 prints
  - 1203 - Annual Report 1997, National Foundation for the Improvement of Education, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Burlington, Vermont, Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1998 March 17-19 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    11 contact sheets, 22 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1204 - Campus Outreach Opportunity League (COOL), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1998 May 2 (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - 1155 - Winter Report 1998, IDA, Steve Wewerka, photographer (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - 1155 - Winter Report 1998, IDA, Steve Wewerka, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 365)
  - 1205 - Native American Film and Video Festival, Smithsonian National Museum of the American Indian, New York City, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1998 October 30-November 3 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    6 contact sheets, 13 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1206 - Blackside Inc., Hopes on the Horizon: The African Media Project, Boston, Massachusetts, Tony Gonzalez, 1998 April 8 (Box 19, Folder 204)
    6 contact sheets, 14 prints
  - 1207 - Spring 1998, Vietnam: Do Thi Binh and Artist Dang Thi Khue, Field Office, Thea's Story, Nguyen Hong Sam, photographer (Box 19, Folder 205)
    3 contact sheets, 2 5x7 color prints
  - 1207 - Spring 1998, Vietnam: Do Thi Binh and Artist Dang Thi Khue, Field Office, Thea's Story, Nguyen Hong Sam, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 366)
  - 1208 - Fall 1998 - Hands Holding Declaration of Human Rights, James Hamilton, photographer - Agreement (Box 19, Folder 206)
  - 1208 - Fall 1998 - Hands Holding Declaration of Human Rights, James Hamilton, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 367)
  - 1209 - General Obasanjo Addressing Trustees, Martin Dixon, photographer, 1998 September 23 (Box 19, Folder 207)
  - 1210 - Annual Report 1998, Theda Skocpol at Harvard, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC) - Religion, Stella Johnson, photographer (Box 19, Folder 208)
    6 black and white contact sheets, 3 5x7 prints
  - 1210 - Annual Report 1998, Theda Skocpol at Harvard, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC) - Religion, Stella Johnson, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 368)
  - 1211 - Annual Report 1998, Philippines, Multiple Grantees - photocopies of photographs by Edwin Tutay (Box 19, Folder 209)
    1. Soil and Water Conservation Foundation, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Governance and Public Policy
    2. Kauswagan Community Social Center, Assets, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH)
    3. Cebu Uniting for Sustainable Water, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Governanace and Civil Society (GCS) and Assets Community and Resource Development (CRD)
    4. Mag-uugmad Foundation Assets Community and Resource Development (CRD)
    5. University of San Carlos Assets, HDRH
    2 5x7 black and white prints, photocopied photos
  - 1211 - Annual Report 1997, Philippines Field Office, Assets and Peace and Social Justice (PSJ) (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - 1211 - Annual Report 1998, RGAs, Philippines, Multiple Grantees, Edwin Tutay, photographer (Box 19, Folder 211)
  - 1211F - Annual Report 1998, Cebu Uniting for Sustainable Water, Philippines, Peace and Social Justice, Governance and Civil Society, Community and Resource Development (Box 19, Folder 212)